<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="rules">
        The objective of Wahoo is to move each of your marbles from their starting positions, around the board and into their home positions.
        \n\nThe game begins by each player rolling the dice.  If the player rolls either a 6 or a 1, the player may move one marble from the starting position to the player’s starting corner.  The player may then roll the dice again.  If the player does not roll a 6 or 1, it is the next player’s turn.  The turns move clockwise.  Each player will continue to roll once each turn until the player has rolled a 6 or 1 and can leave the starting position.
        \n\nOnce the player has a marble “out,” he/she will roll the dice once each turn and then move the number of holes on the dice.
        \n\nIf the player rolls a 6 or 1, he/she will move the number of spaces and then roll again.  If the player continues to roll a 6 or 1, the player will continue to roll until a number that is not a 6 or 1 is rolled.  There is no limit to the amount of times a player may roll again.  When a player is able to roll again, he/she is not confined to move the marble previously moved.  Instead, the player may move any marble to player owns that can legally move.
        \n\nIf a player rolls a number that would cause him/her to jump over or to land on one of his/her own marbles, this player may not move this marble.
        \n\nIf a player rolls a number that lands in a hole that is occupied by a different player, the player occupying the hole is “knocked off” and returned to his/her starting position.
        \n\nIf a player is able to move, the player must move even if this is undesirable.  A player is not allowed to skip a turn if there is a legal move to be made.
        \n\nIf there is no legal move to be made, the player cannot move and it is the next player’s turn.
        \n\nThe game ends when any player is able to move all 4 marbles into his/her home positions.  If a player is close to home, but roles a number too high and there is no available hole, the player is unable to move and it is the next players turn.

    </string>
</resources>